{
    "subject": "resource/Nyai_Ahmad_Dahlan",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Siti Walidah (1872 \u2013 31 May 1946), better known as Nyai Ahmad Dahlan, was a female emancipation figure, wife of Muhammadiyah founder Ahmad Dahlan, and National Heroine of Indonesia.",
    "human_readable": "The abstract of Nyai Ahmad Dahlan is Siti Walidah (1872 \u2013 31 May 1946), better known as Nyai Ahmad Dahlan, was a female emancipation figure, wife of Muhammadiyah founder Ahmad Dahlan, and National Heroine of Indonesia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8257362842559814,
            "question": "What is Nyai Ahmad Dahlan best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.815110445022583,
            "question": "Who was Nyai Ahmad Dahlan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7976788878440857,
            "question": "Who was Nyai Ahmad Dahlan married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7887999415397644,
            "question": "How is Nyai Ahmad Dahlan remembered in Indonesia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7797385454177856,
            "question": "What title was given to Nyai Ahmad Dahlan by Indonesia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7243705987930298,
            "question": "What movement was Nyai Ahmad Dahlan involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6619187593460083,
            "question": "What years did Nyai Ahmad Dahlan live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6279163956642151,
            "question": "What role did Nyai Ahmad Dahlan play within Muhammadiyah?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6054426431655884,
            "question": "What year did Nyai Ahmad Dahlan pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5689345002174377,
            "question": "Who was the founder of Muhammadiyah?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The abstract of Nyai Ahmad Dahlan is Siti Walidah (1872 \u2013 31 May 1946), better known as Nyai Ahmad Dahlan, was a female emancipation figure, wife of Muhammadiyah founder Ahmad Dahlan, and National Heroine of Indonesia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7536_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did Nyai Ahmad Dahlan pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7536_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did Nyai Ahmad Dahlan play within Muhammadiyah?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7536_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What years did Nyai Ahmad Dahlan live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7536_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7536_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7536_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7536_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7536_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7536_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7536_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7536_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7536_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7536_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7536_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation for the triple:\n\n* Subject: Nyai Ahmad Dahlan\n* Predicate: abstract of\n* Object: Siti Walidah (1872 \u2013 31 May 1946), better known as Nyai Ahmad Dahlan, was a female emancipation figure, wife of Muhammadiyah founder Ahmad Dahlan, and National Heroine of Indonesia.\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention multiple occurrences of Nyai Ahmad Dahlan's history, which includes her being a female emancipation figure, wife of Muhammadiyah founder Ahmad Dahlan, and National Heroine of Indonesia. This matches the provided object, Siti Walidah (1872 \u2013 31 May 1946), better known as Nyai Ahmad Dahlan, was a female emancipation figure, wife of Muhammadiyah founder Ahmad Dahlan, and National Heroine of Indonesia.\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe provided context information clearly describes Siti Walidah (1872 \u2013 31 May 1946), better known as Nyai Ahmad Dahlan, as a female emancipation figure and the wife of Muhammadiyah founder Ahmad Dahlan. Additionally, it confirms her status as a National Heroine of Indonesia, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}